wordego.com 2018-02-27

# Privacy Policy – Wordego Ad Exchange

Wordego Privacy Policy is an inseparable part of the Wordego Online Programs. Before you register to participate or to use the services provided in scope of any of the Wordego Online Programs, please read the Wordego Privacy Policy clauses carefully. Registering to participate or to use the services provided in scope of any of the Wordego Online Programs, means that you have accepted the Wordego Privacy Policy clauses, and the legal rights and obligations born from this policy.

If you don't accept the clauses of the Wordego Privacy Policy, please do not register to participate or to use the services provided in scope of any of the Wordego Online Programs. 

We want you to clearly know how we use your information gathered during your registration to participate or to use the services provided in scope of the WORDEGO PROGRAMs, and how you can protect your privacy. 

2.1. We use the information we gather through all services within the WORDEGO PROGRAMs; to provide, maintain, protect and enhance our services, to develop new services, and to protect both WORDEGO and our PROGRAM participants and users. We also use these information to provide contents special to you, like more relevant SEARCH results and ADs.   
2.2. We may use the user name, e-mail, address, telephone and other information that you have provided during your registration to participate or to use the services provided in scope of the WORDEGO PROGRAMs, in all our services in respect to the WORDEGO PROGRAMs. Besides, we may change your previous records, to have you registered on our systems with up-to-date information.   
2.3. When you contact WORDEGO, we may keep record of all your communication logs with the aim of helping to resolve the problems you might be facing. We may use your communication information to give you information and to send you our announcements and promotion messages.   
2.4. We use the information gathered through cookies or other technologies, to improve user experience and to enhance the general quality of our services.   
2.5. We ask your permission prior to using your personal information for purposes other than the ones that have been stated in this PRIVACY POLICY.   
2.6. WORDEGO may process personal information in servers located in many countries around the world. We may process your personal information in a server located in a country other than you reside in.   
2.7. We may share the indiscrete and personally unidentifiable information publicly and with people and organizations that we cooperate. We may share this information publicly in order to show the trends in the general usage of our services.   
2.8. If WORDEGO merges with another company, acquires a company or disposes its assets, we continue to provide privacy for personal information, and before the personal information is transferred or subject to another PRIVACY POLICY, we notify the users who will be affected from this situation. 

3.1. We aim to provide you to reach your personal information every time you use our services. If these information are wrong, we do our best to help you update or delete them fast (unless we don't have to keep them due to an eligible purpose about operations or legal purposes). When updating your personal information, we may ask you to validate your identification first, before meeting your request.   
3.2. We may decline requests which are unreasonably repeated, requiring disproportional technical effort, endangering the privacy of others or extremely hard in other ways.   
3.3. When we can provide the possibility to access and edit information, excluding those require disproportional level of effort, we do that for free. We try to manage our services in a way to protect them against any accidental or malevolent destruction. Therefore, after you delete your information from our services, we may not delete the remaining copies of them from our active servers, and we may not remove these information from our backup systems. 

We do not share your personal information with individuals, companies and organizations other than the WORDEGO PROGRAM participants. Any situation stated below constitutes an exception for this rule:   
4.1. In case you give permission;   
(a) If we get your permission to do this, we may share your personal information with individuals, companies and organizations other than the WORDEGO PROGRAM participants.   
4.2. To process them externally;   
(a) Based on the instructions in the PRIVACY POLICY and other valid privacy and security precautions, we may give your personal information to our parent company, subsidiaries, affiliates or other reliable organizations or people to process them on our behalf.   
4.3. For legal reasons;   
(a) We may share your personal information with individuals, companies and organizations other than the WORDEGO PROGRAM participants, if we truly believe in good faith that the access, use, protection or disclosure of information is reasonably necessary in the following situations:   
(i) Meeting applicable laws, executions, legal processes or formal obligatory demands.   
(ii) Applying valid service conditions, including researches for possible violations.   
(iii) Identifying, preventing or solving fraud, security issues and technical problems.   
(iv) Protecting rights, property or security of WORDEGO, it’s PROGRAM participants, users or the public, in the ways that laws require or permit. 

5.1. PRIVACY POLICY is valid for all services provided by WORDEGO, it’s parent company, subsidiaries and affiliates.   
5.2. PRIVACY POLICY is not valid for information or ADs shown in the SEARCH results, web sites which may contain WORDEGO services, and information, products and services provided by other companies and individuals. 

6.1. We go through on a regular basis whether the PRIVACY POLICY is being complied or not. We also apply a large number of self-control principles. When we receive a formal complaint message, we get in contact with the complainant to follow the subject. We collaborate with official authorities to resolve all problems about the transfer of personal information, in case we cannot resolve it directly with our PROGRAM participants or users.   
6.2. We work very hard to protect WORDEGO, our PROGRAM participants and users from unauthorized access or unauthorized change, disclosure and destruction of the information we keep.   
6.3. To protect our systems from unauthorized access, we continually revise our information gathering, storing and processing applications including physical security precautions.   
6.4. We limit the access to personal information with WORDEGO employees, subcontractors and intermediaries which are supposed to know this information in order to process them for us, and subject to strict obligations through privacy contracts. 

7.1. The PRIVACY POLICY may change from time to time. We do not make any restriction on your rights under this PRIVACY POLICY, without receiving your clear permission. We publish the changes in the PRIVACY POLICY on this page, and if the changes are important, we provide a more remarkable notification (such as sending an e-mail concerning the changes in PRIVACY POLICY for certain services). We also keep previous versions of this PRIVACY POLICY, so that you can review them later.
